//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Race is identified by:",
        answer: "None of the above",
        options: [
            "Blood",
            "Skin",
            "Ancestry",
            "Genes",
            "All of the above",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which species has the greatest genetic diversity?",
        answer: "Fruit Flies",
        options: [
            "Humans",
            "Chimpanzees",
            "Penguins",
            "Fruit Flies",
            "Elephants",
            "Dogs"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which two populations have the highest average likelihood of sharing genetic traits?",
        answer: "Saudi Arabians and Ethiopians",
        options: [
            "Italians and Ethiopians",
            "Senegalese and Kenyans",
            "Italians and Swedes",
            "Chinese and Lakota(Sioux)",
            "Saudi Arabians and Ethiopians",
            "Germans and Russians"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which continent has the most genetic variety among people?",
        answer: "Africa",
        options: [
            "Europe",
            "Asia",
            "South America",
            "Africa",
            "North America",
            "Antartica"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Greeks believed that the following traits set them apart from 'barbarians':",
        answer: "Language",
        options: [
            "Religion",
            "Skin",
            "Language",
            "Customs",
            "Hairiness",
            "Intelligence"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "John Rolfe, a colonist from Jamestown, and his new bride Pocahontas made headlines in 1619 when they visited the Court of London for the following reasons:",
        answer: "A princess married beneath her status by marrying a commoner",
        options: [
            "An Englishman had married an Indian",
            "A Christian had married a heathen",
            "A princess married beneath her status by marrying a commoner",
            "Londoners had never seen an Indian before",
            "Pocahontas helped struggling English colonist survive in Virginia",
            "Pocahontas was Powhatan Queen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which of the following did NOT play a significant role in how African slavery originally spread over North America?",
        answer: "They were deemed innately inferior",
        options: [
            "As non-Christians, they had no legal protections",
            "They were skilled semi-tropical farmers",
            "The supply of indentured servants from Europe was becoming unreliable",
            "They were deemed innately inferior",
            "Unlike Native Americans, they were resistant to Europeans diseases",
            "They couldn't easily run away"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The factors directly responsible for the birth of the concept of white supremacy in America were:",
        answer: "Declaration of Independence",
        options: [
            "Indian removal",
            "Slavery",
            "Declaration of Independence",
            "The U.S. Constitution",
            "Ancient Greece",
            "Education"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which was NOT a white person's introduction to an Indian?",
        answer: "Democracy",
        options: [
            "An Indian identity",
            "Democracy",
            "Identity by blood quantum",
            "Horses",
            "Measles",
            "Christopher Columbus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What proportion of the $120 billion in house loans gauranteed by the federal government between 1933 and 1962 went to homeowners of European descent?",
        answer: "98%",
        options: [
            "45%",
            "64%",
            "75%",
            "88%",
            "92%",
            "98%"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a result of federal government policies?",
        answer: "Affirmative action quotas",
        options: [
            "Redlining",
            "Urban renewal",
            "Deterioration of inner cities",
            "Affirmative action quotas",
            "The wealth gap between black and white families",
            "Prison Industrial Complex"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Today, the net worth of the average white family is how much compared to the average Black family?",
        answer: "Eight times as much",
        options: [
            "Three times as much",
            "Eight times as much",
            "A third as much",
            "Half as much",
            "Twice as much",
            "The same"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Accordingly to a 1993 study, 86% of suburban whites lived in a community where the Black population was:",
        answer: "Less than 1%",
        options: [
            "Less than 5%",
            "Less than 10%",
            "Less than 1%",
            "More than 10%",
            "More than 15%",
            "More than 20%"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which is NOT an example of a government racial preference program?",
        answer: "1964 Civil Rights Act",
        options: [
            "1964 Civil Rights Act",
            "1862 Homestead Act",
            "1790 Naturalization Act",
            "1934 Federal Housing Administration",
            "1935 Social Security Act",
            "1972 Equal Right Amendment"
        ]
    },
];